[Music]
[âm nhạc]
The wealthy woman is a nun who has
đại phú bà là môn ni cô lô đã biết bao
received countless offerings from the Heavenly Nun. Her family is blessed with
được Thiên Ni cúng dường gia tộc Ba là
offerings from the Heavenly Physician when she gave birth to the
món được thiên y cúng dường khi hạ sinh
child, Tan Bat La Xa La, the
Đồng Tử Tân Bát La Xa La
fourth child.
đứng thứ tư
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
The child, Tan Bat La Xa La, of the
đồng tử tất bát lazara
Brahmin lineage, intelligent and wise, with
dòng Bà La Môn thông minh trí tuệ bốn
pumpkins and sauces, always engaging in reasoning and
mùa bí đỏ tương xô chìm
fighting.
lý luận đánh thế luôn
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
To avoid the changing worldly winds. [
nhằm tránh các phong thế gian thay đổi
Applause] [Music]
[Vỗ tay]
The wealthy woman is a nun who has
đại phú bà là một ni câu lô đã biết bao
received countless offerings from the Heavenly Nun. Her family is
được Thiên Ni cúng dường Gia Tộc bà là
blessed with offerings when she gave birth to the
môn được tin đi cúng dường khi hạ sinh
child. She witnessed Xa Na, not from.
Đồng Tử tận mắt là xa Na đừng từ
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
The action of Tan Bat La Xa
động từ tất bát la
La, each intelligent and wise, with
dong bao la mỗi thông minh trí tuệ bốn
pumpkins and sauces.
mùa bí đỏ tương xô
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
But she herself dares to sleep, bored with the
nhưng tự mình dám ngủ nhàm chán các con
changing worldly winds,
thế gian thay đổi
normally,
thông thường như thế
towards the sealed door
hướng về cửa niêm phong
from where the bird hides in countless good roots.
từ nơi chim khuất trong vô số thiện căn
[Music]
[âm nhạc]